Guide to the Gay U.S.A. Collection MSS.426
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Video recordings, 2000-2012
  - Gay USA 5/5/2005, May 5, 2005; ID: 426.0139; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0139)
  - Gay USA 5/12/2005 - #112, May 12, 2005; ID: 426.0140; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0140)
  - Gay USA 5/19/2005, May 19, 2005; ID: 426.0141; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0141)
  - Gay USA 5/26/2005, May 26, 2005; ID: 426.0142; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0142)
  - Gay USA 6/2/2005, June 2, 2005; ID: 426.0143; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0143)
  - gay USA 6/9/2005, June 9, 2005; ID: 426.0144; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0144)
  - Gay USA 6/16/2005 - Staceyann Chin, June 16, 2005; ID: 426.0145; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0145)
  - Gay USA 6/23/2005, June 23, 2005; ID: 426.0146; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0146)
  - Gay USA 6/30/2005, June 30, 2005; ID: 426.0147; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0147)
  - Gay USA 7/7/2005, July 7, 2005; ID: 426.0148; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0148)
  - Gay USA 7/14/2005, July 14, 2005; ID: 426.0149; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0149)
  - Gay USA 7/21/2005, July 21, 2005; ID: 426.0150; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0150)
  - Gay USA 7/28/2005, July 28, 2005; ID: 426.0151; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0151)
  - Gay USA 8/4/2005, August 4, 2005; ID: 426.0152; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0152)
  - Gay USA 8/11/2005, August 11, 2005; ID: 426.0153; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0153)
  - Gay USA 8/18/2005, August 18, 2005; ID: 426.0154; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0154)
  - Gay USA 8/25/2005, August 25, 2005; ID: 426.0155; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0155)
  - Gay USA 9/1/2005, September 1, 2005; ID: 426.0156; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0156)
  - Gay USA 9/1/2005, September 1, 2005; ID: 426.0157; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0157)
  - Gay USA 9/8/2005, September 8, 2005; ID: 426.0158; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0158)
  - Gay USA 9/22/2005, September 22, 2005; ID: 426.0159; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0159)
  - Gay USA 9/29/2005, September 29, 2005; ID: 426.0160; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0160)
  - Gay USA 10/6/2005, October 6, 2005; ID: 426.0161; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0161)
  - Gay USA 10/13/2005, October 13, 2005; ID: 426.0162; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0162)
  - Gay USA 10/20/2005, October 20, 2005; ID: 426.0163; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0163)
  - Gay USA 10/21/2004 - Barney Frank, October 21, 2004; ID: 426.0164; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0164)
  - Gay USA 10/27/2005, October 27, 2005; ID: 426.0165; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0165)
  - Gay USA 11/3/2005, November 3, 2005; ID: 426.0166; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0166)
  - Gay USA 11/10/2005, November 10, 2005; ID: 426.0167; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0167)
  - Gay USA 11/17/2005, November 17, 2005; ID: 426.0168; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0168)
  - Gay USA 11/24/2005, November 24, 2005; ID: 426.0169; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0169)
  - Gay USA 12/1/2005, December 1, 2005; ID: 426.0170; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0170)
  - Gay USA 12/8/2005, December 8, 2005; ID: 426.0171; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0171)
  - Gay USA 12/15/2005, December 15, 2005; ID: 426.0172; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0172)
  - Gay USA 12/29/2005, December 29, 2005; ID: 426.0173; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0173)
  - Gay USA 1/5/2006, January 5, 2006; ID: 426.0174; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0174)
  - Gay USA 1/12/2006, January 12, 2006; ID: 426.0175; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0175)
  - Gay USA 1/19/2006, January 19, 2006; ID: 426.0176; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0176)
  - Gay USA 1/26/2006, January 26, 2006; ID: 426.0177; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0177)
  - Gay USA 2/2/2006, February 2, 2006; ID: 426.0178; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0178)
  - Gay USA 2/9/2006, February 9, 2006; ID: 426.0179; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0179)
  - Gay USA 2/16/2006, February 16, 2006; ID: 426.0180; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0180)
  - Gay USA 2/23/2006, February 23, 2006; ID: 426.0181; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0181)
  - Gay USA 3/2/2006, March 2, 2006; ID: 426.0182; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0182)
  - Gay USA 3/9/2006, March 9, 2006; ID: 426.0183; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0183)
  - Gay USA 3/16/2006, March 16, 2006; ID: 426.0184; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0184)
  - Gay USA 3/23/2006, March 23, 2006; ID: 426.0185; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0185)
  - Gay USA 3/30/2006, March 30, 2006; ID: 426.0186; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0186)
  - Gay USA 4/6/2006, April 6, 2006; ID: 426.0187; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0187)
  - Gay USA 4/13/2006, April 13, 2006; ID: 426.0188; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0188)
  - Gay USA 4/20/2006, April 20, 2006; ID: 426.0189; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0189)
  - Gay USA 4/27/2006, April 27, 2006; ID: 426.0190; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0190)
  - Gay USA 5/4/2006, May 4, 2006; ID: 426.0191; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0191)
  - Gay USA 5/9/2006, May 9, 2006; ID: 426.0192; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 3, Media ID: 426.0192)
  - Gay USA 5/10/2006, May 10, 2006; ID: 426.0193; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0193)
  - Gay USA 5/24/2006, May 24, 2006; ID: 426.0194; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0194)
  - Gay USA 6/1/2006, June 1, 2006; ID: 426.0195; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0195)
  - Gay USA 6/8/2006, June 8, 2006; ID: 426.0196; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0196)
  - Gay USA 6/15/2006, June 15, 2006; ID: 426.0197; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0197)
  - Gay USA 6/22/2006, June 22, 2006; ID: 426.0198; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0198)
  - Gay USA 6/29/2006, June 29, 2006; ID: 426.0199; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0199)
  - Gay USA 7/6/2006, July 6, 2006; ID: 426.0200; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0200)
  - Gay USA 7/13/2006, July 13, 2006; ID: 426.0201; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0201)
  - Gay USA 7/20/2006, July 20, 2006; ID: 426.0202; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0202)
  - Gay USA 7/27/2006, July 27, 2006; ID: 426.0203; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0203)
  - Gay USA 8/3/2006, August 3, 2006; ID: 426.0204; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0204)
  - Gay USA 8/10/2006, August 10, 2006; ID: 426.0205; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0205)
  - Gay USA 8/17/2006, August 17, 2006; ID: 426.0206; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0206)
  - Gay USA 8/24/2006, August 24, 2006; ID: 426.0207; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0207)
  - gay USA 8/31/2006, August 31, 2006; ID: 426.0208; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0208)
  - Gay USA 9/7/2006, September 7, 2006; ID: 426.0209; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0209)
  - Gay USA 9/14/2006, September 14, 2006; ID: 426.0210; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0210)
  - Gay USA 9/21/2006, September 21, 2006; ID: 426.0211; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0211)
  - Gay USA 9/28/2006, September 28, 2006; ID: 426.0212; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0212)
  - Gay USA 10/5/2006, October 5, 2006; ID: 426.0213; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0213)
  - Gay USA 10/12/2006, October 12, 2006; ID: 426.0214; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0214)
  - Gay USA 10/19/2006, October 19, 2006; ID: 426.0215; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0215)
  - Gay USA 10/26/2006, October 26, 2006; ID: 426.0216; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0216)
  - Gay USA 11/3/2006, November 3, 2006; ID: 426.0217; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0217)
  - Gay USA 11/9/2006, November 9, 2006; ID: 426.0218; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0218)
  - Gay USA 11/16/2006, November 16, 2006; ID: 426.0219; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0219)
  - Gay USA 11/13/2006, November 23, 2006; ID: 426.0220; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0220)
  - Gay USA 11/30/2006, November 30, 2006; ID: 426.0221; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0221)
  - Gay USA 12/07/2006, December 7, 2006; ID: 426.0222; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0222)
  - Gay USA 12/14/2006, December 14, 2006; ID: 426.0223; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0223)
  - Gay USA 12/21/2006, December 21, 2006; ID: 426.0224; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0224)
  - Gay USA 12/28/2006, December 28, 2006; ID: 426.0225; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0225)
  - Gay USA 1/4/2007, January 4, 2007; ID: 426.0226; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0226)
  - Gay USA 1/11/2007, January 11, 2007; ID: 426.0227; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0227)
  - Gay USA 1/18/2007, Jaunary 18, 2007; ID: 426.0228; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0228)
  - Gay USA 1/25/2007, January 25, 2007; ID: 426.0229; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0229)
  - Gay USA 2/1/2007, February 1, 2007; ID: 426.0230; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0230)
  - Gay USA 2/8/2007, February 8, 2007; ID: 426.0231; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0231)
  - Gay USA 2/15/2007, February 15, 2007; ID: 426.0232; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0232)
  - Gay USA 2/22/2007, February 22, 2007; ID: 426.0233; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0233)
  - Gay USA 3/1/2007, March 1, 2007; ID: 426.0234; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0234)
  - Gay USA 3/8/2007, March 8, 2007; ID: 426.0235; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0235)
  - Gay USA 3/15/2007, March 15, 2007; ID: 426.0236; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0236)
  - Gay USA 3/22/2007, March 22, 2007; ID: 426.0237; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0237)
  - Gay USA 3/29/2007, March 29, 2007; ID: 426.0238; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0238)
  - Gay USA 4/5/2007, April 4, 2007; ID: 426.0239; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0239)
  - Gay USA 4/12/2007, April 12, 2007; ID: 426.0240; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0240)
  - Gay USA 4/19/2007, April 19, 2007; ID: 426.0241; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0241)
  - Gay USA 4/26/2007, April 26, 2007; ID: 426.0242; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0242)
  - Gay USA 5/3/2007, May 3, 2007; ID: 426.0243; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0243)
  - Gay USA 5/10/2007, May 10, 2007; ID: 426.0244; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0244)
  - Gay USA 5/17/2007, May 17, 2007; ID: 426.0245; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0245)
  - Gay USA 5/24/2007, May 24, 2007; ID: 426.0246; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0246)
  - Gay USA 5/31/2007, May 31, 2007; ID: 426.0247; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0247)
  - Gay USA 6/7/2007, June 7, 2007; ID: 426.0248; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0248)
  - Gay USA 6/14/2007, June 14, 2007; ID: 426.0249; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0249)
  - Gay USA 6/21/2007, June 21, 2007; ID: 426.0250; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 4, Media ID: 426.0250)
  - Gay USA 6/28/2007, June 28, 2007; ID: 426.0251; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0251)
  - Gay USA 7/5/2007, July 5, 2007; ID: 426.0252; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0252)
  - Gay USA 7/12/2007, July 12, 2007; ID: 426.0253; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0253)
  - Gay USA 7/19/2007, July 19, 2007; ID: 426.0254; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0254)
  - Gay USA 7/26/2007, July 26, 2007; ID: 426.0255; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0255)
  - Gay USA 8/2/2007, August 2, 2007; ID: 426.0256; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0256)
  - Gay USA 8/9/2007, August 9, 2007; ID: 426.0257; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0257)
  - Gay USA 8/16/2007, August 16, 2007; ID: 426.0258; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0258)
  - Gay USA 8/23/2007, August 23, 2007; ID: 426.0259; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0259)
  - Gay USA 9/6/2007, September 6, 2007; ID: 426.0260; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0260)
  - Gay USA 9/13/2007, September 13, 2007; ID: 426.0261; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0261)
  - Gay USA 9/20/2007, September 20, 2007; ID: 426.0262; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0262)
  - Gay USA 9/27/2007, September 27, 2007; ID: 426.0263; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0263)
  - Gay USA 10/4/2007, October 4, 2007; ID: 426.0264; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0264)
  - Gay USA 10/11/2007, October 11, 2007; ID: 426.0265; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0265)
  - Gay USA 10/16/2007, October 16, 2007; ID: 426.0266; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0266)
  - Gay USA 10/25/2007, October 25, 2007; ID: 426.0267; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0267)
  - Gay USA 11/1/2007, November 1, 2007; ID: 426.0268; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0268)
  - Gay USA 11/8/2007, November 8, 2007; ID: 426.0269; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0269)
  - Gay USA 11/15/2007, November 15, 2007; ID: 426.0270; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0270)
  - Gay USA 11/17/2007, November 17, 2007; ID: 426.0271; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0271)
  - Gay USA 11/22/2007, November 22, 2007; ID: 426.0272; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0272)
  - Gay USA 11/29/2007, November 29, 2007; ID: 426.0273; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0273)
  - Gay USA 12/6/2007, December 6, 2007; ID: 426.0274; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0274)
  - Gay USA 12/13/2007, December 13, 2007; ID: 426.0275; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0275)
  - Gay USA 12/20/2007, December 20, 2007; ID: 426.0276; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0276)
  - Gay USA 12/27/2007, December 27, 2007; ID: 426.0277; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0277)
  - Gay USA 1/3/2008, January 3, 2008; ID: 426.0278; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0278)
  - Gay USA 1/10/2008, January 10, 2008; ID: 426.0279; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0279)
  - Gay USA 1/17/2008, January 17, 2008; ID: 426.0280; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0280)
  - Gay USA 1/24/2008, January 24, 2008; ID: 426.0281; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0281)
  - Gay USA 1/31/2008, January 31, 2008; ID: 426.0282; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0282)
  - Gay USA 2/7/2008, February 7, 2008; ID: 426.0283; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0283)
  - Gay USA 2/14/2008, February 14, 2008; ID: 426.0284; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0284)
  - Gay USA 2/21/2008 - Chris Quinn, February 21, 2008; ID: 426.0285; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0285)
  - Gay USA 2/28/2008, February 28, 2008; ID: 426.0286; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0286)
  - Gay USA 3/6/2008 - Cynthia Wade w/ Oscar, March 6, 2008; ID: 426.0287; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0287)
  - Gay USA 3/13/2008, March 13, 2008; ID: 426.0288; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0288)
  - Gay USA 3/20/2008, March 20, 2008; ID: 426.0289; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0289)
  - Gay USA 3/27/2008, March 27, 2008; ID: 426.0290; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0290)
  - Gay USA 4/3/2008, April 3, 2008; ID: 426.0291; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0291)
  - Gay USA 4/10/2008, April 10, 2008; ID: 426.0292; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0292)
  - Gay USA 4/17/2008, April 17, 2008; ID: 426.0293; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0293)
  - Gay USA 4/25/2008, April 25, 2008; ID: 426.0294; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0294)
  - Gay USA 5/1/2008 - Arsham Parsi, May 1, 2008; ID: 426.0295; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0295)
  - Gay USA 5/8/2008, May 8, 2008; ID: 426.0296; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0296)
  - Gay USA 5/15/2008, May 15, 2008; ID: 426.0297; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0297)
  - Gay USA 5/22/2008, May 22, 2008; ID: 426.0298; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0298)
  - Gay USA 5/29/2008 - Bill Thompson, May 29, 2008; ID: 426.0299; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0299)
  - Gay USA 6/5/2008, June 5, 2008; ID: 426.0300; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0300)
  - Gay USA 6/12/2008, June 12, 2008; ID: 426.0301; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0301)
  - Gay USA 6/19/2008, June 19, 2008; ID: 426.0302; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0302)
  - Gay USA 6/26/2008, June 26, 2008; ID: 426.0303; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0303)
  - Gay USA 7/3/2008 - Pride VT (1), July 3, 2008; ID: 426.0304; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0304)
  - Gay USA 7/10/2008 - Pride VT (2), July 10, 2008; ID: 426.0305; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0305)
  - Gay USA 7/17/2008, July 17, 2008; ID: 426.0306; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0306)
  - Gay USA 7/24/2008 - "Title of Show" (2 Guests), July 24, 2008; ID: 426.0307; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0307)
  - Gay USA 7/31/2008, July 31, 2008; ID: 426.0308; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0308)
  - Gay USA 8/7/2008, August 7, 2008; ID: 426.0309; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0309)
  - Gay USA 8/14/2008, August 14, 2008; ID: 426.0310; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 5, Media ID: 426.0310)
  - Gay USA 8/21/2008, August 21, 2008; ID: 426.0311; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0311)
  - Gay USA 8/28/2008, August 28, 2008; ID: 426.0312; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0312)
  - Gay USA 9/4/2008, September 4, 2008; ID: 426.0313; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0313)
  - Gay USA 9/11/2008, September 11, 2008; ID: 426.0314; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0314)
  - Gay USA 9/18/2008 - Mitchell Gold, September 18, 2008; ID: 426.0315; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0315)
  - Gay USA 9/25/2008, September 25, 2008; ID: 426.0316; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0316)
  - Gay USA 10/2/2008 - Kate Clinton, October 2, 2008; ID: 426.0317; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0317)
  - Gay USA 10/9/2008, October 9, 2008; ID: 426.0318; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0318)
  - Gay USA 10/16/2008, October 16, 2008; ID: 426.0319; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0319)
  - Gay USA 10/23/2008, October 23, 2008; ID: 426.0320; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0320)
  - Gay USA 10/30/2008 - Julie Halston, October 30, 2008; ID: 426.0321; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0321)
  - Gay USA 11/6/2008, November 6, 2008; ID: 426.0322; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0322)
  - Gay USA 11/13/2008, November 13, 2008; ID: 426.0323; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0323)
  - Gay USA 11/20/2008, November 20, 2008; ID: 426.0324; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0324)
  - Gay USA 11/27/2008, November 27, 2008; ID: 426.0325; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0325)
  - Gay USA 12/4/2008 - Equality Riders (youths), December 4, 2008; ID: 426.0326; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0326)
  - Gay USA 12/11/2008, December 11, 2008; ID: 426.0327; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0327)
  - Gay USA 12/18/2008, December 18, 2008; ID: 426.0328; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0328)
  - Gay USA 12/25/2008 - Barbara Raab, December 25, 2008; ID: 426.0329; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0329)
  - Gay USA 1/1/2009, January 1, 2009; ID: 426.0330; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0330)
  - Gay USA 1/8/2009, January 8, 2009; ID: 426.0331; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0331)
  - Gay USA 1/15/2009, January 15, 2009; ID: 426.0332; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0332)
  - Gay USA 1/22/2009, January 22, 2009; ID: 426.0333; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0333)
  - Gay USA 1/29/2009, January 29, 2009; ID: 426.0334; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0334)
  - Gay USA 2/5/2009 - Rosie Mendez, February 5, 2009; ID: 426.0335; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0335)
  - Gay USA 2/12/2009, February 12, 2009; ID: 426.0336; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0336)
  - Gay USA 2/19/2009, February 19, 2009; ID: 426.0337; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0337)
  - Gay USA 2/26/2009, February 26, 2009; ID: 426.0338; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0338)
  - Gay USA 3/5/2009, March 5, 2009; ID: 426.0339; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0339)
  - Gay USA 3/12/2009, March 12, 2009; ID: 426.0340; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0340)
  - Gay USA 3/19/2009 - Chris Cooper (Guest host 1), March 19, 2009; ID: 426.0341; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0341)
  - Gay USA 3/26/2009 - Chris Cooper (Guest host 2), March 26, 2009; ID: 426.0342; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0342)
  - Gay USA 4/2/2009, April 2, 2009; ID: 426.0343; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0343)
  - Gay USA 4/9/2009, April 9, 2009; ID: 426.0344; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0344)
  - Gay USA 4/16/2009, April 16, 2009; ID: 426.0345; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0345)
  - Gay USA 4/23/2009, April 23, 2009; ID: 426.0346; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0346)
  - Gay USA 4/30/2009, April 30, 2009; ID: 426.0347; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0347)
  - Gay USA 5/7/2009, May 7, 2009; ID: 426.0348; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0348)
  - Gay USA 5/14/2009, May 14, 2009; ID: 426.0349; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0349)
  - Gay USA 5/21/2009, May 21, 2009; ID: 426.0350; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0350)
  - Gay USA 5/28/2009, May 28, 2009; ID: 426.0351; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0351)
  - Gay USA 6/4/2009, June 4, 2009; ID: 426.0352; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0352)
  - Gay USA 6/11/2009, June 11, 2009; ID: 426.0353; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0353)
  - Gay USA 6/18/2009, June 18, 2009; ID: 426.0354; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0354)
  - Gay USA 6/25/2009 - Cleve Jones, June 25, 2009; ID: 426.0355; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0355)
  - Gay USA 7/2/2009, July 2, 2009; ID: 426.0356; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0356)
  - Gay USA 7/9/2009, July 9, 2009; ID: 426.0357; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0357)
  - Gay USA 7/16/2009, July 16, 2009; ID: 426.0358; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0358)
  - Gay USA 7/24/2009, July 24, 2009; ID: 426.0359; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0359)
  - Gay USA 7/30/2009, July 30, 2009; ID: 426.0360; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0360)
  - Gay USA 8/6/2009, August 6, 2009; ID: 426.0361; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0361)
  - Gay USA 8/13/2009, August 13, 2009; ID: 426.0362; 1 media elements DVCAM (Box 6, Media ID: 426.0362)